<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amezquita Wedding</title>
    <description>Robert &amp; Jen Say I Do
</description>
    <link>http://www.robertandjensayido.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.robertandjensayido.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 21:24:18 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 21:24:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Men</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If Myspace was still around, these guys would easily be in my top 10. Meet the lucky 7 who could get to stand by my side as I wait anxiously at the altar!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/groomsmen/edo.jpg&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; alt=&quot;edo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edward: Best Man&lt;/strong&gt;
“Edo” and “Robbo” have been friends since the fifth grade, when on the school field trip to Balboa Park, a younger version of Ed came up to a younger version of Rob and asked “Why the heck do you play violin?” Instead of taking offense to that question, Rob realized he had a lifelong, best friend in front of him. Through thick and thin, awkward and slightly less awkward phases of life, Rob and Ed form a fearsome duo in Cards Against Humanity. Ed hails from the land of maple leafs and moose, but you would be forgiven for thinking his motherland was Russia after a few drinks as he takes on his (in)famous Russian accent. Edo has taken his dedication to music to a new level, pursuing a PhD in composition at the University of California - Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/groomsmen/matt.jpg&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; alt=&quot;Matt&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt: Groomsman&lt;/strong&gt;
Back when bleached tips were cool, and backpacks with wheels were slightly less cool, Matt and Robert rolled in the deep of middle school as resident orch-dorks (along with Edo of course). Their friendship was cemented when little Robert could not figure out Vivaldi’s triplet-like rhythm from “Spring”, when Matt took pity on him and decided to try and be nice to him. Thankfully, Robert ditched the rolly backpack after trying to make it totally hip, and ever since then, Rob and Matt have been steadfast friends, through distance and Chinchillas. Matt is a mercenary of music and code, throwing down tunes all across California with a variety of groups such as Bogg, putting together fantastic productions with his production company, and coding up company websites on a full stack of awesome, all from the beautiful city of Chico, CA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/groomsmen/kdick.jpg&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; alt=&quot;Kevin D&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kevin D: Groomsman&lt;/strong&gt;
Kevin was one-third of the infamous trifecta of freshman English class, alongside Matt and the other Kevin on this list. But it wasn’t until an especially intense session of studying for AP Biology in the kids section of Barnes and Noble that acquaintance became friendship - it was all fun and games, until M&amp;amp;M’s were involved. Many more adventures followed thereafter - a near cliffhanger at the Elven forest, epic puddle hunting, and Blackout Friday, leveled up Kevin and Rob’s friendship from FF, to BFFs. Though that almost came to an end after one particular session of Left 4 Dead involving a failed jump onto a helicopter. Kev is an IT professional focusing on security, so be careful to not get on his bad side, or else he might L33T HAXX0R your bluetooth connection. While he travels the world debugging other people’s mistakes, he calls the beautiful city of Irvine, CA home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/groomsmen/kweng.jpg&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; alt=&quot;Kevin W&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kevin W: Groomsman&lt;/strong&gt;
Wengster, another third of the infamous trifecta, is a man you can rely on when all else fails. The one who you can talk to about anything at 3 AM for hours, despite having a pressing deadline in less than 6 hours - he’s the guy you make time for, because you just love him that much. His smile, his laugh, and his boyish, lack-of-facial hair good looks endear you, and me, to him. He’s the guy who, after bragging about that totally awesome party you’re gonna get into because he’s in a fraternity-don’t-call-it-a-frat, bro, you’re willing to wait up for 5 hours after he gets arrested for “assaulting” (aka patting on the back) a police officer at a college party (long story short: undercover cops who act like total bros are jerks). KWeng has since cleaned up his act, and after a career change from mechanical engineer to L33T hacker, is now a fellow at Code Reactor in San Francisco, CA, looking to get in on the startup world before the bubble bursts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/groomsmen/groomsmen/akshay.png&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; alt=&quot;Akshay&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Akshay: Groomsman&lt;/strong&gt;
Akshay is a true friend, one who speaks deeply from the heart with you one moment, and drinks deeply from that nasty bottle of whatever you brought over the next. Having met as fellow bioengineers at UC San Diego, Akshay and Rob and three other cool dudes shacked up together for the last two years of college, and along with a bunch of other cool people living practically next door, had some of the craziest nights together. Hitting up all the best electro concerts and beer SD had to offer, conquering Vegas craps tables (well, Akshay at least), and doing a whirlwind tour of Norcal and New England, Akshay is a man’s man, the guy who you would take a punch for - except he’s the one that took it instead, because you were a little distracted. Akshay is now pursing a PhD in Stanford’s Dept. of Bioengineering, working on solving medical imaging so that doctors don’t have to poke around inside you so much, in beautiful Palo Alto, CA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/groomsmen/groomsmen/stefan.jpg&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; alt=&quot;Stefan&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stefan: Groomsman&lt;/strong&gt;
Stefanabanana is a fellow prisoner of PhD studies at Yale University, hailing from the beautiful coast of Florida. Stefan and Rob met after Rob came up to him and a group of other computational biologists commenting about how cool they were, and what classes they were taking. Little did they know that they would end up joining the Kleinstein lab together. After countless hours in a row at hackathons, teaching events, and other group projects, and weekends seeing more of each other than their significant others, somehow, Rob and Stefan are still the best of friends and partners - mostly thanks to Stefan’s immense amount of patience with Rob when he throws up crazy-stupid ideas. Partners in crime in solving everything from online learning, to predicting patient readmissions, and finding you a super sweet flight deal from JetBlue, Stefan is a member of the Kleinstein lab in the Computational Biology &amp;amp; Bioinformatics program, and together with Rob they will persevere through to the bittersweet end of the PhD!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/groomsmen/groomsmen/mikey.jpg&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; alt=&quot;Mikey&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mikey: Groomsman&lt;/strong&gt;
Mikey has a heart of gold, a guy who values family, friends, and the happiness of others above all else. Well, unless you dig into his Kona Mud Pie, then all bets are off. Kidding aside, Mikey never has anything but a smile on his face, and wears his heart on his sleeve. However, that same heart doesn’t seem to know what sports team to root for because he switches teams like the clothes on his back - twice a day, and sometimes thrice. After many trips together to exotic locales such as Hawaii, Tahoe, and Disneyland, Mikey and Rob care for one another like brothers, and don’t need the workings of the law to call each other just that. Mikey works in the services industry all across America’s finest city - San Diego, CA.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 10:34:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.robertandjensayido.com/wedding/posts/2015/09/10/meetthegroomsmen.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.robertandjensayido.com/wedding/posts/2015/09/10/meetthegroomsmen.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>wedding</category>
        
        <category>posts</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the &#39;Maids</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s no way Jen could say her I Do’s without these amazing ladies. These beautiful bridesmaids have been there for all important stages of life. The stunning seven are not only down-to-earth and fun to be around, they’re hardworking go-getters who excel in life. Get to know the bridal party!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/bridesmaids/Siyi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Siyi&quot; /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Siyi: Maid of Honor&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Siyi and Jen met in college when UCSD decided that putting these two in the same room was a good idea. They instantly clicked over marching band (they both played clarinet) and High School Musical (and they both love Zac Efron). From that night on, the CPiCs, Crazy Partners in Crime, have been known for their outrageous “How-To” videos, weekend long foodventures, and celebrity filled activities. Siyi is from Fremont, CA and is currently a Research Associate for a stem cell lab at UCSF.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/bridesmaids/Karissa.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Karissa&quot; /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Karissa: Bridesmaid&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Karissa and Jen have known each other since their bando days in the high school marching band. The two coolest clarinet players joined forces with Christina and have been BFFFs ever since. Even though Karissa and Jen haven’t lived in the same state since high school, they continue to stay close through their hilarious texts, occasional cruise vacations, and annual sushi date with “Sheila” aka Christina. Karissa lives in Omaha, Nebraska, where she provides counseling services as an Outpatient Therapist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/bridesmaids/Christina.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Christina&quot; /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Christina: Bridesmaid&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Christina and Jen have known each other since they were 10, when they played on the same softball team. They remained friends throughout high school and together with Karissa, the three BFFFs have maintained a tight-knit friendship. In college, Christina and Jen were roomies at the famous “Cheddabush” house, where they continued playing softball together and laughing at all of the ridiculous things Christina says. Christina currently works as an Insurance Claims Assistant in America’s Finest City, San Diego, CA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/bridesmaids/April.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;April&quot; /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;April: Bridesmaid&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
April is Robert’s sister and Jen’s future sister-in-law. April and Jen may have only known each other for a short while, but it doesn’t stop them from sharing laughs over the Amezquita dogs and Robert’s weird antics. When the two of them are in town, they like to take a break from their pesky brothers and catch up over Mrs. Amezquita’s delicious food. April is a Storyboard Artist for the prestigious Nickelodeon’s Artist Program in Los Angeles, CA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/bridesmaids/Jess.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Jess&quot; /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Jess: Bridesmaid&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Jess and Jen became friends at UCSD, when Jen picked up Jess as her Little Sis in Phi Sigma Rho. The “Princess and Precious” duo immediately became known for their #adorable pictures and their “obnoxious” poses. They bonded over food, fun, and photobombing as many pictures as possible. Jess resides in Orange County, CA, where she’s a Rehabilitation Aide, studying to become a Physical Therapist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/bridesmaids/Grace.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Grace&quot; /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Grace: Bridesmaid&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Grace and Jen met in college when the both of them were pledging for Phi Sigma Rho. They’ve literally taken their friendship from coast to coast, as the both of them now live on the east where they’ve adopted the fashion-forward east coast style. From hanging out in NYC and Boston to keeping it low key in CT and NH, the distance has only helped these two CA girls become closer. Dr. Grace is currently an Optometrist in Nashua, New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/page_images/bridesmaids/Gab.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Gab&quot; /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Gab: Bridesmaid&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Gab is Jen’s oldest childhood friend. Growing up, these two were inseparable, constantly begging their parents to let them have ANOTHER sleepover so they could play Barbies and watch the Spice World movie. They continue to have one of the strongest friendships (20+ years!) and now beg their parents to let them lay in the middle of the cul-de-sac at night, so they can reminisce about the fun they had as kids. Gab is a recent Psychology graduate from UCSD and is now traveling around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 10:34:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.robertandjensayido.com/wedding/posts/2015/09/10/meetthebridesmaids.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.robertandjensayido.com/wedding/posts/2015/09/10/meetthebridesmaids.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>wedding</category>
        
        <category>posts</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
